[
    {
        "question":"Where is the JavaScript placed inside an HTML document or page?",
        "ans1":"In the <body> and <head> sections.",
        "ans2": "In the <meta> section.",
        "ans3": "In the <title> section",
        "ans4": "In the <footer> section.",
        "correct":"In the <body> and <head> sections."

    },

    {
        "question":"In JavaScript, what element is used to store multiple values in a single variable?",
        "ans1":"Strings",
        "ans2": "Arrays",
        "ans3": "Variables",
        "ans4": "Functions",
        "correct":"Arrays"

    },
    {
        "question":"What is the name of the statement that is used to exit or end a loop?",
        "ans1":"Break statement",
        "ans2": "Falter statement",
        "ans3": "Conditional statement",
        "ans4": "Close statement",
        "correct":"Break statement"

    },
    {
        "question":"What tag is used to define the metadata about an HTML document, and must always be included inside the element?",
        "ans1":"<div>",
        "ans2": "<img>",
        "ans3": "<table>",
        "ans4": "<meta>",
        "correct":"<meta>"

    }
    ,{
        "question":"What tag is used to define an interactive field where users can enter data?",
        "ans1":"<input>",
        "ans2": "<datalist>",
        "ans3": "<dialog>",
        "ans4": "<enterpoint>",
        "correct":"<input>"

    },
    {
        "question":"What tag is used to define – and place – an interactive button in an HTML document?",
        "ans1":"<footer>",
        "ans2": "<clickfield>",
        "ans3": "<button>",
        "ans4": "<td>",
        "correct":"<button>"

    },
    {
        "question":"What tag is used to define an unordered list that is bulleted?",
        "ans1":"<s>",
        "ans2": "<li>",
        "ans3": "<u>",
        "ans4": "<ul>",
        "correct":"<ul>"

    },
    {
        "question":"Cass can be used to greatly improve the ____ of an HTML form.",
        "ans1":"Appearance",
        "ans2": "Performance",
        "ans3": "Layout",
        "ans4": "Colors",
        "correct":"Appearance"

    },
    {
        "question":"What is the CSS property that is used to specify the edges of a table?",
        "ans1":"Margins",
        "ans2": "Borders",
        "ans3": "Boxes",
        "ans4": "Fill",
        "correct":"Borders"

    },
    {
        "question":"External stylesheets are stored in what type of files?",
        "ans1":"XML",
        "ans2": "PHP",
        "ans3": "HTML",
        "ans4": "CSS",
        "correct":"CSS"

    }
]